tenderfields.com 2017-08-11

# Privacy Policy | Protecting Our Customers Data | Tenderfield, Australia

## Tenderfield Pty Ltd

This Privacy Policy sets out the commitment by Tenderfield Pty Ltd (ACN 153 858 649), its successors and assignees (referred to as **we, us** and **our** ) to protect the privacy of your personal information that we collect through our websites [www.tendefield.com](https://www.tenderfield.com/) and [www.tenderfield.com.au](https://www.tenderfield.com.au/), third party websites, mobile devices and any other device that you may use to access any of our products and services that does not have a separate privacy policy (collectively the **Website** ) or directly from you, being the person, organisation or entity that uses the Website (referred to as **you** or **your** ).

Privacy Policy | We are committed to protecting the personal information we collect from you because we understand the importance of keeping your personal information confidential and secure. We use your personal information for the purpose of responding to your enquiry and supplying you with a service.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. You providing us with personal information indicates that you have had sufficient opportunity to access this Privacy Policy and that you have read and consented to it.

All information that we collect, including your personal information, is stored on our secure servers located in our offices in Sydney, Australia, and on other secure cloud servers and offline storage facilities that we use, which may be located outside Australia. Please feel free to contact us should you require any further information on how we manage your personal information.

### Why do we require your personal information?

The personal information collected and maintained by us is necessary for the products and services that we provide to you. Any information collected may be used to investigate any possible breach of our Terms and Conditions or breach of any law.

### The type of information we will collect about you

##### Registration information:

When you create an account with us, you are required to provide at least the following information to us: 

  * your company/business name;
  * your company identification/registration number;
  * your personal name; and
  * your contact details including email address, address and telephone number.

You may also create an account with us using a third party such as Facebook and LinkedIn. If you create an account using this method, we will collect your personal information by accessing the personal information you have stored with these third parties.

Depending upon which of our products and services you choose to use, we may also require you to provide us with your:

  * biometric information;
  * banking details, credit card details and other financial information;
  * date of birth;
  * gender;
  * tax number;
  * preferences and opinions; and
  * any other information requested on the Website or otherwise requested by us or provided by you.

##### Information you choose to share:

We may collect any additional information you choose to share on the Website such as your profile information and when you publish a project and upload tender documents. It also includes the information you choose to share when you take an action, such as when you add an approved head contractor or sub-contractor to your account.

When you upload a file using our services, you are entirely responsible for what you store on our storage facilities and who you share these files with. We may access any file you store on our storage facilities to ensure proper delivery of products and services.

##### Other information we receive about you:

We also receive other types of information about you:

  * we receive data about you whenever you interact with the Website, such as when you search for a head contractor or a sub-contractor or click on an advertisement;
  * when you post tenders on the Website, we may receive additional related data (or metadata); and
  * we receive data from the computer, mobile phone or other device you use to access the Website. This may include your IP address, location, the type of browser you use, or the pages you visit.

##### Address book and calendar syncing:

You may upload your address book (including email and contact number details) as well as your calendar to the Website. By doing so we will use this information for example by helping you to manage your projects by providing you a template to invite your contacts to become account holders with us, or by allowing you to share your address book contacts with other account holders.

### Purpose of collection

When reasonably necessary we will collect and use your personal information for one or more of the following functions/activities:

  * internal record keeping;
  * providing products and services to you or to someone else you know;
  * processing an application you have made;
  * improving our products and services;
  * direct marketing, including providing you with information about new products or services, special offers or other information that we, our related entities and affiliates offer that may be of interest to you; and
  * undertaking various activities required by law.

### Methods of collection

Personal information will generally be collected directly from you through the use of any of our standard forms, over the Internet, via email or through a telephone conversation with you. 

##### How we use cookies and web beacons:

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Website.

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We may use cookies to monitor usage of the Website and to create a personal record of when you visit the Website and what pages you view so that we may serve you more effectively. We may also use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve the Website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

We may use web beacons on the Website from time to time. Web beacons or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behaviour and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page.

### Disclosure of your personal information to third parties

We may seek the services of third party suppliers of goods or services to carry out specialised activities. Where your personal information is provided to these third parties to enable them to perform their agreed activities, they are required to use the personal information provided only for the service they supply.

We only provide personal information to third parties if we consider that the third party can comply with the standards in our Privacy Policy.

Other than the above, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorised or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate a suspected unlawful activity or for such other reasons as allowed by law.

### Internet users

If you access the Website, we may collect additional personal information about you in the form of your IP (Internet Protocol) address and domain name. Also, the Website may use cookies.

### Security

We store your personal information in different ways, including in paper and in electronic form. The security and protection of your personal information is important to us. We take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is stored safely to protect it from misuse, interference, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure, including electronic and physical security measures.

If we no longer need your personal information for the purpose of which it was obtained we will take all reasonable steps to destroy the information and ensure the information is de-identified.

No information transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. We cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us, or receive from us. The transmission and exchange of information is carried out at your own risk. Although we take measures to safeguard against unauthorised disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Your Rights and Access

**Choice and Consent:** Providing us with your personal information is optional to you. You can choose not to provide personal information. When you provide us with your personal information, you consent to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**Access:** You may access the personal information we hold about you, upon making a written request. We will respond to your request for access within 30 days.

**Refusal:** We may refuse a request for access to personal information where the law requires or allows us to do so (for example, information relates to legal proceedings). You will be notified of this refusal and the reasons for the refusal in a notice in writing to you.

**Notification:** If upon receiving access to your personal information or at any other time, you believe the personal information we hold about you is not accurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please notify us immediately. We will take all reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is not accurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading.

**Correction:** You have the right to correct personal information that we hold about you, including information which is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. We rely in part upon customers advising us when their personal information changes. We will respond to any request within a reasonable time. We will endeavour to promptly correct any information found to be inaccurate, incomplete or out of date.

**Unsubscribe:** To unsubscribe from our e-mail database, or opt out of any communications, please contact us with “Unsubscribe” in the subject line of the e-mail.

### Links to other websites

The Website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave the Website, you should note that we do not have any control over those other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such websites and such websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Failure to provide information

If the personal information you provide to us is not accurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, we may be unable to provide you, or someone else you know, with the services you, or they, are seeking.

### Privacy Inquiry/Complaints

If you have an inquiry or complaint, please contact us by email to[ info@tenderfield.com ](mailto:info@tenderfield.com).

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

From time to time it may be necessary for us to review and revise our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time, should this occur the amendment would be posted on the Website.

For questions and notices, please contact us at:

#### Tenderfield Pty Ltd

Address: Level 1, 271 Alfred Street North, North Sydney, NSW 2060 Australia

Telephone: 1300 72 40 45

Email: [ info@tenderfield.com ](mailto:info@tenderfield.com)

Last updated: 11th August 2016
